Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 51, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Recognition: a source book on labor for teachers and students, 1978; Publication (Box 51, Folder 46)
    Author: Charles J. O'Leary; Bill Murphy; John R. Hanson
  - Item 2: Recognition: a source book on labor for teachers and students, 1973; Publication (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Box: 51, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: From fireside to factory, 1916; Publication (Box 51, Folder 47)
    Author: Meta Lilienthal
- Box: 51, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: An illegal boycott: argument of Arthur Lord of counsel for the plaintiff in the case of Benjamin S. Atwood vs. Brockton Central Labor Union et als. and the findings of the master as set forth in his report to the court., 1906; Publication (Box 51, Folder 48)
    Author: Arthur Lord
- Box: 51, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: New frontiers for labor, Publication (Box 51, Folder 49)
- Box: 51, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: The role of the labor unions in the Russian Revolution, Publication (Box 51, Folder 50)
- Box: 51, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: A talk between two workers, 1933; Publication (Box 51, Folder 51)
    Author: Errico Malatesta
- Box: 51, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Unemployed councils in St. Petersburg in 1906, 1931; Publication (Box 51, Folder 52)
    Author: Sergei Vasilyevich Malyshev
- Box: 51, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Open the factories, 1921; Publication (Box 51, Folder 53)
- Box: 51, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: The church the enemy of the workers: Rome is the natural ally of all exploiters, 1942; Publication (Box 51, Folder 54)
    Author: Joseph McCabe; Emanuel Haldeman-Julius
- Box: 51, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Sport first aid, Publication (Box 51, Folder 55)
    Author: Melinda J. Flegel
- Box: 51, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: The low-wage challenge to global growth: the labor cost-productivity imbalance in newly industrialized countries, 1990; Publication (Box 51, Folder 56)
    Author: Walter Russell Mead
- Box: 51, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: The fight for steel, 1931; Publication (Box 51, Folder 57)
    Author: N. Mikhailov
- Box: 51, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Struggle in the coal fields, 1974; Publication (Box 51, Folder 58)
    Author: Kim Moody
- Box: 51, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Where is the CIO going?: A program for militant trade unionism, 1949; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Item 2: Labor unity: what AFL-CIO merger means for workers, 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Item 3: Conspiracy to Strangle Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Item 4: Labor and anti-semitism, 1953; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Item 5: The Trotskyite fifth column in the labor movement, 1945; Publication (Box 51, Folder 59)
- Box: 51, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Wyndham Mortimer meets the Soviet auto workers, 1961; Publication (Box 51, Folder 60)
    Author: Wyndham Mortimer
- Box: 51, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Stopping a war: the fight of the French workers against the Moroccan campaign of 1925, 1926; Publication (Box 51, Folder 61)
- Box: 51, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Jews in the U.S.A.: Jewish workers and the middle class Jewish culture: integration and assimilation: Zionism and the state of Israel Jewish unity, 1960; Publication (Box 51, Folder 62)
    Author: P. Novik
- Box: 51, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Socialism and the trade unions: the present needs and future functions of labor organizations, 1931; Publication (Box 51, Folder 63)
- Box: 51, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The 153 year struggle for the American Labor Party, 1980; Publication (Box 51, Folder 64)
    Author: Leon Trotsky
- Box: 51, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Profit-sharing: or, The worker's fair share, 1919; Publication (Box 51, Folder 65)
    Author: George W. Perkins
- Box: 51, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The case of the Rand School., 1919; Publication (Box 51, Folder 66)
    Author: Rand School of Social Science
- Box: 51, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Union growth reconsidered; a critical analysis of recent growth theories, 1961; Publication (Box 51, Folder 67)
- Box: 51, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Labor's position and the Southern mills: being a reprint of articles by Harry Riemer, 1930; Publication (Box 51, Folder 68)
    Author: Harry Riemer
- Box: 51, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: The miners' road to freedom, 1935; Publication (Box 51, Folder 69)
    Author: Anna Rochester; Pat Toohey
- Box: 51, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: The Supreme Court and the minimum wage, 1923; Publication (Box 51, Folder 70)
- Box: 51, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Labor-credit: a property owners solution of the unemployment problem, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 71)
    Author: Carroll Morgan Salls
- Box: 51, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Shut down: 15 early warning signs of plant closure, 1981; Publication (Box 51, Folder 72)
    Author: Coalition to Stop Plant Closings
- Box: 51, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: A positive program for laissez faire; some proposals for a liberal economic policy, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 73)
    Author: Henry Calvert Simons
- Box: 51, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The machine, 1924; Publication (Box 51, Folder 74)
- Box: 51, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Address: The Condition of the laboring population of America and their true interests., Publication (Box 51, Folder 75)
    Author: E. G. Squier
- Box: 51, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Labour politics in U.S.A., 1949; Publication (Box 51, Folder 76)
    Author: Mark Starr; Margaret Cole
- Box: 51, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Steel mill or treadmill?: How to stop the big steel steal: the facts about wages, prices, profits and unionism in the steel and metals industries, 1971; Publication (Box 51, Folder 77)
- Box: 51, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: The worker as a consumer: how he is exploited, how he may protect himself, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 78)
    Author: Mark Starr; Helen Norton
- Box: 51, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: West Coast longshoremen and the "Bridges Plan", 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 79)
    Author: C. Thomas
- Box: 51, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Toward revolutionary mass work, 1932; Publication (Box 51, Folder 80)
- Box: 51, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: One big union: an outline of a possible industrial organization of the working class with chart, Publication (Box 51, Folder 81)
- Box: 51, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Ethics and American unionism: and the path ahead for the working class, 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 82)
    Author: Sam Weiner
- Box: 51, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Paper trade terms: a glossary for the allied trades, 1947; Publication (Box 51, Folder 83)
    Author: William Bond Wheelwright
- Box: 51, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Who is Sidney Hillman?: biographical series on Sidney Hillman, 1944; Publication (Box 51, Folder 84)
- Box: 51, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Why every worker should join the Communist Party, 1930; Publication (Box 51, Folder 85)
- Box: 51, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Why a workingman should be a socialist, 1912; Publication (Box 51, Folder 86)
    Author: Gaylord Wilshire
- Box: 51, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Marx and America, 1934; Publication (Box 51, Folder 87)
- Box: 51, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Spies in the trade unions, 1904; Publication (Box 51, Folder 88)
- Box: 52, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: British trade unions and collective bargaining since the Second World War, 1966; Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Author: Shirley W. Lerner
- Box: 52, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The uprising of the 20,000, 1979; Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Author: Donna Ippolito; Anne Pride
- Box: 52, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor's stake in the fight against "right to work", 1977; Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Author: Paddy Quick
- Box: 53, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Socialism Made Easy, 1909; Publication (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Author: James Connolly
- Box: 53, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Federal Courts and the Writ of Injunction in Labor Controversies, Publication (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Author: James M. Beck; Daniel Davenport
- Box: 53, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: For Bread, Peace and Freedom, 1949; Publication (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
- Box: 53, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Address to the General Master Workman, 1885; Publication (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Author: Knights of Labor
    Notes: October 5, 1885
- Box: 53, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Unionism and Socialism, 1904; Publication (Box 53, Folder 5)